(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
PLEASE WAIT...
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Mixed Nuts
Official Hige Dandism
袋に詰められたナッツのような
Like nuts packed in a bag
世間では誰もがそれぞれでああだれかと寄り添い合ってる
In this world, everyone is huddling with someone or other
そこに紛れ込んだ僕らはピーナッツ
We, who have mixed in there, are like peanuts
みたいに木の実の振りしながら
While pretending to be tree nuts
微笑み浮かべる
We put on a smile
幸せのテンプレートの上 文字通り絵に描いたうわべの中
On the template of happiness, within a literal picture-perfect facade
テーブルを囲んで笑うその時さえ ありのままではいられないまま
Even when laughing around the table, we can't remain as we truly are
隠し事だらけ 継ぎ接ぎだらけのHome, you know
A home full of secrets and patchwork, you know
噛み砕いてもなくならない本音が 歯に挟まったまま
True feelings that don't go away even if chewed, stuck in our teeth
不安だらけ 成り行き任せのLife, and I know
A life full of anxiety and left to chance, and I know
仮初めまみれの日常を抜けて ここに僕がいてあなたがいる
Escaping the everyday life full of transient things, I am here and you are here
この真実だけでも胃がもたれてゆく
This truth alone is enough to give me indigestion
化けの皮剥がれた一粒のピーナッツみたいに
Like a single peanut whose disguise has been stripped away
世間から一瞬で弾かれてしまう そんな時こそ
When we're cast out from society in an instant, that's exactly when
曲がりなりでよかったら側にいさせて 共に揺られ揺られ踏まれても
If it's okay for me to be imperfect, let me stay by your side, even if we're tossed and stepped on together
割れない殻みたいになるから
Because we'll become like a shell that won't break
生まれた場所の木の上か 地面の中かそれだけの違い
Whether it's on a tree or in the ground, that's the only difference in where we're born
許されないほどみだらなこの世界を 等しく願えますように
I hope we can wish for this world, so lewd it's unforgivable, equally
時に冷たくて 側が湿るのも, you know
Even when it's cold sometimes and our sides get damp, you know
星のひとつも見つからない 雷に満ちた日があってもいい
It's okay to have days filled with thunder where not even a single star can be found
ミスだらけ アドレナリン任せのShow, but I know
A show full of mistakes and left to adrenaline, but I know
所詮ひとかけの日常だから 腹の中にでも流してるよ
It's just a fragment of everyday life after all, so I'm just washing it down into my stomach
隠し事だらけ 継ぎ接ぎだらけのHome, you know
A home full of secrets and patchwork, you know
とっておきも出来合いもぶち込んで かき混ぜて平らげながら
Throwing in the special and the ready-made, mixing it up while finishing it off
普通なのない 正解なのないLife, and I know
A life with no normal, no right answer, and I know
仮初めまみれの日常を抜けて ここに僕がいてあなたがいる
Escaping the everyday life full of transient things, I am here and you are here
この真実だけでも胃がもたれてゆく
This truth alone is enough to give me indigestion
このひとつまみの奇跡を噛み締めてゆく
I'll savor this pinch of a miracle
ADAMAS
LiSA
大気迷土にシビレ切らした 不純の闇 怒号の渦の中
Tired of the atmospheric labyrinth, in the midst of impure darkness and a vortex of roars
始まりに孤独は付き物さ
Loneliness is a constant at the beginning
芯の底からも壁をぶち破れ 期待外れ 風向きかき回せ
Break through the walls from the very core, defy expectations and stir up the wind
加速していくマグマの鼓動 確かめて進め
Confirm the accelerating heartbeat of magma and move forward
イヤついた
I'm fed up with it
悲劇のような声がする
A voice like a tragedy is heard
僕らは始まった 栄光のゴールに向かってさ
We have begun, towards the goal of glory
Shiny sword, my diamond 悲しみと願いの結晶体に僕らは誓う
Shiny sword, my diamond, we swear upon the crystal of sorrow and prayer
それぞれの光を目指してゆく 何度だって立ち上がってゆくんだ
Aiming for our respective lights, we'll stand up again and again
It's time. Wake up! この祈りが革命の確証さ 輝け
It's time. Wake up! This prayer is the proof of revolution, shine!
えー！ レッツゴー！
Eh! Let's go!
朝を眠りに捨てて過ごした日
Spending days throwing away mornings to sleep
灰色の空 嫌い見上げては歌う
Hating the gray sky, I look up and sing
ガラス細工 巧みに施した ショコラ と きらめき
Glasswork with skillfully applied chocolate and sparkles
時めくほど眩しい奇跡を
A miracle so dazzling it makes my heart throb
世界が待ってる
The world is waiting
Shine so my diamond
純粋と希望の結晶
A crystal of purity and hope
Shine so my tears
強くなる光を秘めてる
Harboring a light that grows stronger
まがい物あふれる時間は
The time filled with imitations
とっくに笑い飛ばそう
Let's laugh it off already
等身の個性に磨いた
Polished into a life-sized individuality
不屈の勲章 燃え尽きるまで
An unyielding medal, until it burns out
No way to prove
Just follow through
(Oh my way)
Don't break it now
Don't break it, let me breathe
守りたいもの守り抜くだけ
I'll just protect what I want to protect to the end
No way to prove
Just follow through
(Oh my way)
So I will keep on going, keep on going
(Let me breathe)
真っ赤に熱く輝いて
Shining red and hot
Shine so my diamond
悲しみと願いの結晶
A crystal of sadness and wishes
僕ら明日をしか
Our tomorrow is...
それぞれの誇りを目指してく
Aiming for our respective prides
何度だって立ち上がっては
No matter how many times we stand up
明日をゆくんだ
We'll go towards tomorrow
It's time, it's time, 鼓動の音が
It's time, it's time, the sound of the heartbeat
革命の結晶さ輝け
Is the crystal of revolution, shine!
It's time, it's time, ademas
Don't say "lazy"
Ho-kago Tea Time
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当は crazy
Because in reality, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう
The swans are just like that
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
They're paddling their feet where they can't be seen
本能に忠実 忠実
Faithful to instinct, faithful
翻弄も重々承知
Well aware of the playfulness
前頭葉から出した
Taken out from the frontal lobe
宝の持ち腐れ禁止なんです
Wasting talent is strictly forbidden
目の前の景色に誘われてゆく先
To the destination lured by the scenery before me
秩序をマークして
Marking the order
視界に荒れそな笑顔弾ける翼もあれちょっと
Smiles bursting in the field of vision, even those wings, wait a bit
指先を追って ぐるり放射した
Following the fingertips, it radiated around
それだけでなんか達成感
Just with that, there's some sense of achievement
大事なのは自分可愛がること
The important thing is to cherish yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ他人も愛せない
If you don't love yourself, you can't love others
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当は crazy
Because in reality, I'm crazy
能ある鷹はそう
A talented hawk is just like that
見えないとこにピック隠すんです
It hides its pick where it can't be seen
想像に一生懸命
Trying hard in imagination
現実は絶体絶命
Reality is a desperate situation
発展途上らしい
Apparently, I'm still developing
だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
That's why I suddenly go off-pitch
画面に映らないだけでやる気はメーター振り切って
Even if it's not shown on screen, my motivation is off the charts
いつでも全力で夢見たそのあとも
Always dreaming with all my might, even after that
全力で眠って
Sleeping with all my might
準備中って言って 凝視しすぎた
Saying "in preparation" and staring too much
それだけでなんで敗北感
Why is there a sense of defeat just from that?
健気にも今日を 妥協せずに生きて
Living today admirably without compromising
柔軟に臨機応変千変万化っち
Flexible and resourceful, ever-changing
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当は crazy
Because in reality, I'm crazy
だって本当はcrazy
Because actually, I'm crazy
クジャクたちはそう
Peacocks are like that
ここぞという時　紐を結ぶんです
When it really counts, they tie their shoelaces
五臓の　Moshimoshi
A greeting from the viscera
願望は　修行精神
My wish is a training spirit
誘惑は　外伝だし
Temptations are just side stories
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんだ
That's why my will breaks so easily
やば、まさかオーライ？
Oops, could it be 'all right'?
いいや、ギリクリヤー
No, barely cleared it
それだけで　なんて満足なの
Just with that, I'm so satisfied
大事なのは自分
The important thing is myself
認めてゆくこと
To keep on accepting
自分を許さなきゃ
If I don't forgive myself
人も許せない
I can't forgive others either
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当はcrazy
Because actually, I'm crazy
クジャクたちはそう
Peacocks are like that
見えないところでバタ足するんです
They paddle their feet where they can't be seen
本能に　忠実
Faithful to instinct
煩脳も　重々承知
Fully aware of worldly desires
前途は洋々だし
The future is bright
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんだ
That's why I take breaks once in a while
EXPOSE 'Burn out!!!'
RAISE A SUILEN
Next up!
Are you guys ready!?
EXPOSE 'Burn out!!!'
言葉の端から
From the edges of words
舌を舐めずりぐらい
As if licking my lips
主語を並べて
Lining up the subjects
Aiming for...
笑顔で共存
Coexisting with a smile
Count down　差し伸べて
Count down, reach out
仮面の正体
The true identity of the mask
言い合いやってる
Having an argument
Showdown!　How's it happen?
不名誉な魂胆とレトリック
Dishonorable motives and rhetoric
暗示を
The hints
提示を
The presentation
偽り合ってんの？　被害は何なの？
Are we lying to each other? What's the damage?
見据えろ正体
Stare at the true identity
LET'S DO THE WASH IT!
SHOWDOWN!　SHOWDOWN!　何が？
SHOWDOWN!　SHOWDOWN!　What is?
守るべきものの顔　今すぐ
The face of what must be protected, right now
剥ぎ取らせて
Let me strip it away
獣みたいに叫べよ
Scream like a beast
YOU CAN CHANGE THE WORLD!
僕たちの歌で
With our song
WELCOME TO US!
LET IT GO!　LET IT GO!　LET IT GO!
限界突破勝負はBAN! BAN!
Surpassing limits, the battle is BAN! BAN!
正々堂々　真っ向砕け
Fair and square, smash them head-on
限界突破勝負はBAN! BAN!
Surpassing limits, the battle is BAN! BAN!
既成概念をバイバイ
Bye-bye to stereotypes
お口を開ければ
When you open your mouth
吹き出すモヤモヤ　Hey!
Out come the fuzzy feelings, Hey!
不満ばかりぞろり
Nothing but complaints lining up
眩しい！
Dazzling!
反らして引いたんだ
I turned away and pulled back
希望　いつの間に
Hope... before I knew it
火花が踊り出し　はしゃぐ
Sparks start dancing and frolicking
SHOWDOWN!　HIGH!　ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
お得意の言い訳並べていいわね
You're good at lining up your favorite excuses, aren't you
暗示を
The hints
大事に
Carefully
独走は綺麗？　また　孤食も飽きちゃったんだ
Is solo running beautiful? Also, I'm tired of eating alone
見据えろ正体
Stare at the true identity
前ならえはNO!
Falling in line is a NO!
SHOWDOWN!　SHOWDOWN!　なら今
SHOWDOWN!　SHOWDOWN!　Then now
守るべきものの顔　今すぐ
The face of what must be protected, right now
研ぎ澄ませて
Sharpen it
獣みたいに吠え散らすに
Howling like a beast
YOU CAN CHANGE THE WORLD!
僕たちの歌で
With our song
WELCOME TO US!
物言えぬ意味
A meaning that cannot be spoken
察しもしなせよ
Don't even try to guess
ここで
Right here
目を覚ませテンション
Wake up the tension
開始の合図を
The signal to start
今すぐ曝け出せ
Expose it all right now
獣の如く正直に
Honestly, like a beast
叫べよ　You can change the world
Scream it out, You can change the world
今すぐ曝け出せ
Expose it all right now
獣の如く叫べよ
Scream like a beast
You can change the world
僕たちの歌で
With our song
Welcome to our show
Let it go, let it go, let it go
拳を上げろ　全てを壊せ
Raise your fists, destroy everything
常識なんて　打ち砕け
Smash common sense to pieces
拳を上げろ　全てを壊せ
Raise your fists, destroy everything
犠牲者たちに　バイバイ
Say bye-bye to the victims
Don't wanna wait
Mark my words and remember that time
Look at me properly and remember that time
Attention Please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Are you by any chance a MERAKYats who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine, and I'm going to be here explaining briefly what is going on with Pavolia Reine's Membership, (that is mine, by the way).
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights,
which you can constantly show off everytime you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties
which also means membership exclusive streams in which we can have various talks, play games together and do other miscellaneous members involvements.
Like what, you might ask...? Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed but it is a part of our character development training
in which we aim to build a community of people who like living dangerously.
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
震えてる手を見つめて
Gazing at my trembling hands
咲き萎んだみたい
It’s like I’ve bloomed and withered
煉獄のほとりで
By the edge of purgatory
幕は下りて
The curtain falls
霧煙る夜
On a misty, smoky night
浮かべ赤い月
A red moon floats in the sky
睨んで私を
Glare at me
目を逸らさないで
Don't look away
黒い鉄格子のなかで
Inside the black iron bars
私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born
悪意の苗床　願い望むがままにお前に
A seedbed of malice, just as you wish and desire
さあ　期待に応えて　壊して
Now, meet my expectations and destroy it
腐る前に
Before it rots
因果の代償を払い
Pay the price of karma
共に行こう　名前のない怪物
Let's go together, nameless monster
何をしてる
What are you doing?
苦情もうるさくて
Even the complaints are loud
思い出せないの
I can't remember
あの日の戦慄
The shiver of that day
雨は鳴り止まない
The rain won't stop ringing
何にも見えないの
I can't see anything
ほら見てごらん
Come, take a look
大きくなったろ
I've grown bigger, haven't I?
この雨降らすこの空
This sky that brings this rain
私は奪われないもう
I won't be robbed anymore
響き割れたノイズを愛す牢罪を感謝達に
Loving the cracked noise, a sin of confinement, I offer my thanks
それは震う正義を
That trembling justice
不正な生き様を抱きしめて
Embracing a dishonest way of life
この身体を受け入れ灯り行こう名前のない灯火
Accepting this body, let's light the way, a nameless flame
鳴り響く音の中で
Amidst the ringing sounds
私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born
悪意の代償を願い望むがままに憂いあり
Wishing for the price of malice, there is sorrow as desired
そう当てよう正義を
Yes, let's apply justice
伸ばしたその腕に因果の代償を払い
Paying the price of karma to that outstretched arm
向くようなガラクタだぜ
It's just like some piece of junk
この雨降らすこの空
This sky that brings this rain
私は奪われないもう
I won't be robbed anymore
響き割れたノイズを愛す牢罪を感謝達に
Loving the resonant cracked noise, a sin of confinement, I offer my thanks
それは震う正義を
That trembling justice
不正な生き様を抱きしめて
Embracing a dishonest way of life
この身体を受け入れ灯り行こう名前のない灯火
Accepting this body, let's light the way, a nameless flame
Woo!
I hope you guys are having fun so far!
What do you guys think?
What do you guys think about this outfit?
This is the first time you guys are seeing this one, right?
The last one, the one before this...
You saw that last time when I was doing the...
When I was doing the thing.
The thing.
But, yeah! This is new.
You know, the other outfit, I'm wearing a, you know, a pair of short pants.
And I thought to myself, "You know, maybe I'll just get myself, you know, to wear a skirt, a dress!"
Look at this! So cute, right?
We have a ribbon on top of my head...
Which is new.
You know, we have this hairpin, even though we have a ribbon...
You know, can't have Reine without the hairpin, I think.
And we have this tie.
So cute!
Yeah!
And these shoes!
Ready to step on things such as, you know...
...the floor, grass, etc.
And these socks! You know, so cute, right?
Look at this!
Look at that!
Yeah!
Hope you guys like it.
Hope I surprised you enough with this.
And I'm gonna, I'm just gonna twirl so you guys can see it.
You know, I mean you guys could see it before this, but...
...you know, look closely so you guys can see.
I'm gonna twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl...
Twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl, twirl...
Yeah! You see, that's what the back part looks like.
(Sighs) But yes, welcome to our first talking segment.
What should I talk about? How's the weather today?
How's the weather today? Yeah.
Well, you know what? I guess we should move to the next song, right?
Hope you guys are staying hydrated,
because we still have much more!
Odo / Ado
半端ならK.O.
If you're half-hearted, it's a K.O.
Woah, woah, woah したいならどうぞ
If you want to say "Woah, woah, woah," go right ahead
開演前場内 お泣きも笑っても愛してね
Inside the venue before the show starts, love me whether I'm crying or laughing
ほら 鳴らせ 手を 響かせろ
Come on, clap your hands, let them ring out
なんだかなってツァンナイ こと丸出しよ
It's like, I'm just showing everything out in the open
Lonely lonely no no とはにかみ本気出そう
Saying "Lonely lonely no no" with a shy smile, let's get serious
やんなっちゃってドロに 紅白だらけ
I'm sick of it, covered in mud and red and white
溺れて 堕ちて
Drowning, falling
Hey そろそろ Wake Up!
Hey, it's about time to wake up!
もっと頑張って
Work harder
アガるまでもっと頑張って
Work harder until you get fired up
繋がろう ひとりよりふたり べったらづけ
Let's connect, two is better than one, like Bettara-zuke
心配ないや Alright 探せ ドンマイ
Don't worry, alright, look for it, don't mind
アイノリで ノっけちゃえば
If we just get on board together
案外サクっといっちゃいそう
It seems like it'll go surprisingly smoothly
半端ならK.O.
If you're half-hearted, it's a K.O.
Woah, woah, woah したいならどうぞ
If you want to say "Woah, woah, woah," go right ahead
開演前場内 お泣きも笑っても愛してね
Inside the venue before the show starts, love me whether I'm crying or laughing
ほら 鳴らせ 手を 響かせろ
Come on, clap your hands, let them ring out
宵は暗転パーティ
Tonight is a blackout party
踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Start dancing, start dancing
孤独は殺気まりおねっと
Solitude is a murderous marionette
イトにまわれ おしえられ
Spin on the strings, being taught
どこかでバイバイ Let's go
Saying bye-bye somewhere, let's go
どんな劣等感だって即興の血漿で
No matter what kind of inferiority complex it is, with improvised plasma
抑え込んで ツッ込んで 終われそう
Suppressing it, thrusting it, it seems like it'll end
Oh yeah! Up and down アテンション
Oh yeah! Up and down, attention
目舞っちゃっての疎通
Communicating while feeling dizzy
ドバっと吹き出すのは 本能の火種
What's gushing out is the spark of instinct
別に興味ない 特に関係ない
I'm not really interested, it doesn't really matter
塞ぎ込んで ザッツ・ポジティブ
Feeling down? That's positive!
合図を奏でて 震える 夜を
Playing the signal, through the trembling night
纏まって 穿とう
Coming together, let's break through
泣いていこう
Let's keep on crying
半端ならK.O.
If you're half-hearted, it's a K.O.
踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Start dancing, start dancing
孤独は殺気まりおねっと
Solitude is a murderous marionette
イトにまわれ おしえられ
Spin on the strings, being taught
今宵もアクセル・バニラ
Tonight as well, accel vanilla
またどこかを 傷つけ
Hurting somewhere again
次回まで お元気で
Stay well until next time
ここらでバイバイ Let's go
Saying bye-bye here, let's go
FIRE BIRD / Roselia
空がどんな高くても
No matter how high the sky is
羽が毟り取れても
Even if my wings are torn off
飛び立つこと 恐れずに
Without being afraid of taking flight
焦がせ 不死なる絆
Burn it up, our immortal bond
Fly to the sky... FIRE BIRD!
ついに夢へ 燃え上がれ！
Finally, to the dream... Blaze up!
Burning Heart
不意に降りた絶望もどうか怖がらないで
Even the despair that suddenly descends, please don't be afraid.
あなたの胸いつだって灯す夢があるから
Because there is always a dream that lights up in your heart.
駆逐されるような
As if being exterminated,
残酷な現実
a cruel reality.
だけどそれは愛故の
But that is because of love,
生命の調べ
the melody of life.
燃え上がる火焔より不死鳥（フェニックス）のように
Like a firebird, more than a burning flame,
We are... 何度だって強くなった夢は負けない
We are... The dream that has become strong many times will not lose.
貴方を連れて行きたいんだ絶世の地平へ
I want to take you to the peerless horizon.
逆境に負けない希望を 記そう
Let's record hope, hope that doesn't lose to adversity.
その音の風で
With the wind of that sound...
そして新世界へ Burning Heart
And to a new world! Burning Heart!
Burning Heart
不自由なあの世の答えはまだ分からず
Still not knowing the answer to that unfree world,
だけど前に 前だけに きっと光は射す
but surely light will shine only forward, always forward.
頂点（テッペン）を問うと
Questioning the peak,
透明になるほど
becoming so clear,
不完全に輝く
it shines in its imperfection.
この魂（ほのお）に...
Into this soul...
舞い上がる暁に 煌めく太陽のように
Like the glittering sun in the rising dawn,
We are... 闇から逃げず 支え燃える紅蓮の炎
We are... The crimson flame that doesn't run from darkness, supporting and burning.
幾千回眠ってもいいから その手を伸ばせば
Even if you sleep thousands of times, if you reach out that hand,
羽に変わるんだと信じて 勇気を
believe that it will turn into wings, and take courage.
信じて勇気を
Believe and take courage,
そして明日へ
and move towards tomorrow.
最初は上を見ること
At first, looking up,
それ望むこと怖かった
it was scary to wish for that.
籠の中から銀河は遠く
From inside the cage, the galaxy was far away.
その星の輝きに憧れて
Longing for the brightness of that star...
ただ眩しくて
Just dazzling,
ただ悔しくて
just frustrating.
だけど今は一歩 ここから
But now, taking one step from here.
羽ばたこう 頂点の夢へと！
Let's fly towards the dream of the peak!
燃え上がる火焔より不死鳥（フェニックス）のように
Like a firebird, more than a burning flame,
We are... 再び誓う 頂点（テッペン）へのミッション
We are... Vowing once again the mission to the peak.
貴方を連れて行きたいんだ絶世の地平へ
I want to take you to the peerless horizon.
情熱の楽園まで 生き抜こう
Let's live until we reach the paradise of passion.
生き抜こう
Let's live on.
音楽を地図に歌え 新世界へ
With music as a map, sing to the new world!
Burning Heart
Invincible Rainbow Arrow
A-Set
空飛ぶカップ　パラレルマップ
Flying cups, parallel maps,
タイムトリップ　君にだけ　教えよう
A time trip; only to you will I show them.
消えないデカ　溶けない理科
The detective who won't vanish, science that won't melt,
不死身のピカ　君になら分かるはず
An immortal flash; you should be able to understand.
大人たちは顔背ける　ビターな目　曇らせてる
The adults turn their faces away, their bitter eyes clouded over.
だけど僕らだけ知ってる　信じる力
But only we know the power of believing,
奇跡起こすこと
And how it makes miracles happen.
たとえ悪魔が　君を誘惑してもきっと
Even if a devil should tempt you, surely...
夜空駆け抜ける女神
The goddess racing through the night sky,
虹の翼でラリアット
Will deliver a lariat with rainbow wings!
この世界が　君を消し去ろうとしても
Even if this world tries to erase you,
レジスト　僕が光追い越して　君を守るよ
Resist! I will overtake the light and protect you!
異界の列車　秘密の結社　呪いの術者　君となら...
Otherworldly trains, secret societies, users of curses... with you...
心にそっと　触れた焦燥　迫るリミット　あの瞳　届くかな
The impatience that softly touched my heart, the approaching limit; will I reach those eyes?
大人たちは昨日を忘れ　檻の中　閉じこもってる
The adults forget yesterday, locked away in their cages.
だけど僕らだけ知ってる　愛する炎　すべて溶かすこと
But only we know that this loving flame will melt everything.
たとえ誰かが　夢を奪おうとしても
Even if someone tries to steal your dreams,
ちょっと！
Wait a minute!
輝く瞳があれば　君は無敵の　ピラミッド
As long as you have sparkling eyes, you're the invincible... pyramid!
たとえ宇宙が　夢を葬ろうとしても
Even if the universe tries to bury your dreams,
レボルト　僕らの信じる気持ち　決して負けやしない
Revolt! Our feelings of belief will never suffer defeat!
愛の火は消せない
The fire of love can never be extinguished!
イリスは神のメッセンジャーが　君を導く
Iris, the messenger of the gods, will lead you
虹のアーチ　一緒に灯そう　時を超えて
To the rainbow arch; let's light it together, across time.
大人たちは顔背ける　ビターな目　曇らせてる
The adults turn their faces away, their bitter eyes clouded over.
だけど僕らだけ知ってる　信じる力　奇跡起こすこと
But only we know the power of believing, and how it makes miracles happen.
たとえ悪魔が　君を誘惑してもきっと
Even if a devil should tempt you, surely...
夜空駆け抜ける女神
The goddess racing through the night sky,
虹の翼でラリアット
Will deliver a lariat with rainbow wings!
この世界が　君を消し去ろうとしても
Even if this world tries to erase you,
レジスト　僕が光追い越して　君を守るよ
Resist! I will overtake the light and protect you!
虹のよう　終わらない
Like a rainbow, it never ends!
Hi! How are you guys doing now?
Hope you guys doing okay. Stay hydrated!
Thank you so much for... Fire Bird!
I asked some help from my talented, talented, talented friends.
Thank you so much to Kiara, Ollie, Moona, and Kobo...
...for helping me with the choruses as well as the solo parts.
We sang so many songs today, so many songs.
But well, there's still, there's still some, some things, you know, it's not over yet obviously.
Well, uh, I don't know. What do you guys think about this?
What time do you think it is?
Nice.
Well, I heard you loud and clear, even though it's in your heart.
The uh, it's time for the long-awaited segment of this live...
...I've been dying to like, I've been dying to like...
...uh, just like vomit everything out of my mouth.
It is time for some istigamarating of...
Drumroll, please!
Prrrrrrr... in your heart, drumroll.
Prrrrrrr!
You guessed it right! It is time for...
...Birthday Goods Announcement! Woo!
Pa-pa-pa-paaa!
Look at that beautiful, beautiful illustration.
We have multiple items today.
We have the spicy 1000 ReineMat...
...and the GWS+. Very nice, right?
I uh, you know, origin-, um, that came from my brain.
I'm sure you guys love the name. Yes.
It's a big, big, big, big rubber mat and...
...you know, look at this. It's a, yes, super big size.
So maybe if you guys are used to small rubber mats, well this one's big...
...so you know, big is good, I guess.
Uh, yeah, because its size is 60 by 90...
...and look at that beautiful art from Pochi-mama.
Look at that, my super neat room. No mess, so nice, right?
Yeah, what are you waiting for? Don't you want your own Reine room in your room?
Then you know what to do.
Spicy, so so so spicy. Reine's spicy room in your spicy room.
And the second one, we also have a drinking mug, extra extra extra large size.
That's why, you know, today the theme is kind of big.
We have the small Raines, but our merch is big.
Our drinking mug is actually extra large size with approximately 1-liter volume.
So all of you, like, thirsty people, don't worry, you will never get thirsty...
...as long as you watch Reine while you drink from this mug, okay?
Look at that beautiful, beautiful, beautiful art.
Look at that, so cute.
You would want one. Or two, or three, you know. It's alright.
Any amount is okay.
And yeah, if you buy the merch as a set, you will get a bonus postcard.
Which is very, very, very similar to the rubber mat...
...except it has a different expression.
Look at that, so spicy. What a spicy expression.
And it comes with a handwritten autograph. Can you imagine it?
Handwritten autograph in my Reine merch!
Tunggu apa lagi, mudah sekali.
What are you waiting for, it's so easy.
So easy, guys. What are you waiting for?
You know, I don't know if goods sales is open yet, but what are you waiting for?
If it's not open, you know, just like be on standby.
You know what to do. And yeah, so on the corner of the postcard...
...you know, there'll be like a nice, nice signature, so cute, Reine.
You know, you want your own authentic Reine signature, right?
Yes, autograph, autograph, autograph.
Yes, so that is it, you know, after seeing this, you know, if you don't think...
"Oh, it's so cute, it's so spicy, I wanna buy it," then you will think that soon.
So, you know, just like be on standby and buy it as soon as it's available.
Okay, okay, okay, okay. Yay!
Listen, listen, listen.
This is not the end yet.
You guys are here looking at, you know, how beautiful the whole thing is, the whole stage is.
Oh, yes. Thank you so much, Kanauru, for making this happen.
Well...
This is not the end.
After this, there will be one more song.
Well, what song is it gonna be? Another one of those...
...well you know, another cover song?
No.
Reine finally singing her original song. Oh my god, really?
And not just an original song, I'm gonna be singing my new original song...
...which will be available starting September 10, 00:00 at your local time.
So get ready for that.
Have you guys, are you guys ready?
Your mouse is like, "I'm ready as soon as it's available," you know.
Yes!
It's an English song, it's the very, very, very first time
I'm singing an English song, and it's gonna be
the first time you guys will be hearing this song
for the first time here. Okay?
Okay, what are you waiting for? So easy, muda sekali...
Okay, what are you waiting for? So easy, very easy...
...just sit back and listen and sing along maybe,
and dance along. Let's go!
Are you guys excited?
Get ready for Illusion Night!
Illusion Night
Pavolia Reine
Kiss me, keep those lips from wandering off
Tell me every sweet and tender thought
Give me all you have to give and more
Fantasies where futures are born
Can you feel the beat, the rhythm, the tune?
Your heart and mine, the countdown
If you feel something coming to you
Believe it and scream it all out!
I don't think I'll miss you any more
like I did the day you left
There's so many just like you I could use instead
'Cause passion burning brightly hurts you in the end
Instead I'll swallow the pain
Tomorrow's another today
Curtain calls at dawn, darling showtime
Spend the moment dancing in the moonlight
Till your gaze starts swaying with my body
Keep your eyes on me
Take me somewhere deep into the night
Touch me here, there, anywhere you like
Trust me, won't you let me look inside?
Fantasies and futures collide
It's just the two of us beneath the starry sky
If the only way to keep on living is keep on living strong
Then you can keep the kindness 'cause I'm moving on
No use to say goodbye to me, I'm already gone
So wipe all your tears away
I know we'll start over someday
Curtain calls at dawn, darling showtime
All your heart, your soul, your body
You belong to one and only
Unconditionally yearning
Knowing no one else will do
Can you feel the bond between us grow tight?
We're closer than we've ever been
Follow me, match your rhythm to mine
And let it all out from within
I don't think I'll miss you any more
than I did the day you left
I won't say I love you, I know I'll take it back
I'm used to this, I'm not the same old little bird
Burned from flickering candles and then could never last
Instead of living in past
Forward's the perfect place for lovers like us
to take a chance
There's nothing here to stop us when in rom-romance
And I won't let you leave me alone without a doubt
I don't want to hear a goodbye
Don't break the illusion tonight
Curtain calls at dawn, darling showtime
Stay forever living till the sunrise
Feel so lucky even with the lights off
Dance until we drop
THANK YOU
My M-chan, Kanauru, Farhan, Chroneco, Holoro
This is for you
Thank you so much for always supporting me
I will keep doing my best!
[AD SPOT]
Reine's Original Song Illusion Night out 9/9 23:59!
Reine's Birthday Merch NOW on SALE
オリジナル曲 Pavolia Reine's 「Illusion Night」 10月10日 00:00 リリース！
Original Song: Pavolia Reine - 'Illusion Night' | Releasing Oct 10 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9 (JST)
Pavolia Reine 誕生記念2022 | 9月9日 販売開始
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
オリジナル曲 Pavolia Reine's 「Illusion Night」 10月10日 00:00 リリース！
Original Song: Pavolia Reine - 'Illusion Night' | Releasing Oct 10 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9 (JST)
Pavolia Reine 誕生記念2022 | 9月9日 販売開始
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
オリジナル曲 Pavolia Reine's 「Illusion Night」 10月10日 00:00 リリース！
Original Song: Pavolia Reine - 'Illusion Night' | Releasing Oct 10 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9 (JST)
Pavolia Reine 誕生記念2022 | 9月9日 販売開始
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
オリジナル曲 Pavolia Reine's 「Illusion Night」 10月10日 00:00 リリース！
Original Song: Pavolia Reine - 'Illusion Night' | Releasing Oct 10 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9 (JST)
Pavolia Reine 誕生記念2022 | 9月9日 販売開始
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
オリジナル曲 Pavolia Reine's 「Illusion Night」 10月10日 00:00 リリース！
Original Song: Pavolia Reine - 'Illusion Night' | Releasing Oct 10 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9 (JST)
Pavolia Reine 誕生記念2022 | 9月9日 販売開始
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
オリジナル曲 Pavolia Reine's 「Illusion Night」 10月10日 00:00 リリース！
Original Song: Pavolia Reine - 'Illusion Night' | Releasing Oct 10 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9 (JST)
Pavolia Reine 誕生記念2022 | 9月9日 販売開始
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
オリジナル曲 Pavolia Reine's 「Illusion Night」 10月10日 00:00 リリース！
Original Song: Pavolia Reine - 'Illusion Night' | Releasing Oct 10 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9 (JST)
Pavolia Reine 誕生記念2022 | 9月9日 販売開始
Pavolia Reine Birthday Celebration 2022 | On Sale September 9
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 「Illusion Night」 September 10, 2022 00:00 RELEASE!
Pavolia Reine's ORIGINAL SONG 'Illusion Night' | RELEASE Sept 10, 2022 at 00:00!